ご視聴ありがとうございました
Seen, Maru
When Ansen uses it, when Ansen doesn't use it.
She's doing her makeup.
She is eating a meal.
Thank you for watching!
Ekimae ekimae naka ekimae ekimae platform
Even if they say it's easy mode
I don't care what they say.
I feel like I've been here before
Déjà vu all over again
Just below the line of fire.
Squeaky clean.
It was like a value.
I'm still stuck between left and right
We're not ready to go out into the world
First of all, we're leaving now.
I'm off!
I'm the only one here
I thought I'd be the only one here.
But there's quite a lot of staff here.
I'm relieved.
YouTube material
This is it.
Please hold fast.
Thank you for your time
I need about half an hour
Thank you very much
You'll have a light nice soon from now on.
Oh, what's this? It's amazing!
Who wrote this?
Lighten up.
Like this.
Thank you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you Happy birthday dear Nanako
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you.
Always a favorite kids' culture
The best of the best!
Thank you!
I'm so happy for you
I'll take it later
Thank you very much.
The last one?
Thank you very much
Can I take one more picture?
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Yes, that's all I have to say.
Thank you very much.
It's okay. It's okay.
I can see it. I can see it. I can see these stories.
It's scary to hear about a room like this.
It's something, but Train's calm, too.
It's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's an encore. We're doing our best to have fun.
And your mom, too. She went out of her way.
She had a meeting with me during the rehearsal, and we're going to do a contraption in the morning.
That's great. She thought of it.
Actually, it was from here, but wow, it came from here.
She was thinking that she was close to being serious.
You're right.
You're right, you're right.
Maybe you have a better downward brain than I do.
I'll do my best.
Once we get through all that, we'll be doing something really fun.
I knew this culture existed
We have this culture.
It didn't last.
I knew it was Nonotan's turn.
I knew it. She's a serious person.
That's for sure.
So maybe next time...
Because he's serious.
That's true.
Then let's have him check it out.
I'll check.
After the check, Yamane checks.
Let's have him check.
Yes, I'm going up the mountain.
Yes, sir.
Yes, we are waiting for you.
Hello.
Yes, I am starting to get nervous well.
Yes, but I am calmer than last year.
Collaboration lablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablablabla.
Imagine this
Italy Italy Italy Italy
Evituna Evituna
Evituno Nonocoma.
ITALY ITALY ITALY ITALY
Italy Italy Italy Italy
Evituna Evituno.
Evituno Nonocoma.
ANNIE
I've started! Yamamoto-kun is on the stage!
Are you ready to have fun?
Yamamoto-kun had a great first meeting!
I want to do my best!
I'm going to the princess.
I'll be fine until we've talked.
That's great.
I went down for an encore.
It's a little creepy.
Me.
me... me...
me